Guide to the Martin Wong Papers ca. 1982-1999 MSS.102
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Artwork, 128374
  - Subseries A: Art by Wong and Wong's Sketchbooks, 128385
    - Sketch: winged figure, undated; 128394 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Sketch: tattoo flash, undated; 128393 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Sketch: "I Think I'm Going to be Sick" (1983), 128392 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Sketches: interiors, undated; 128391 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Drawings: auction items (series), undated; 128390 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Drawings: playing cards, undated; 128389 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Drawing: sun-dial, undated; 128388 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Sketch: moon & stars, undated; 128387 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Sketch: "Hypnos & Thanatos", undated; 128386 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Sketchbook, undated; 256626 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Poem in Sign Language, undated; 256771 (Box 15)
      Scope and Contents
      This item is a scroll that contains a poem written by Wong and represented with drawings of American Sign Language signs for letters instead of with the Latin alphabet.
      The poem reads:
      Nutzboy claimed he never washed
      cause soap makes you soft
      even poured salt down
      my back once to prove it
      his body had the strong odor
      of cypress and axle grease
      and whenever he'd ripened
      I'd get drunk off the smell
      One look at his eyes and you just
    - Poem in Sign Language, 1983-10-27 (Box 15)
      Things we never knew time without end.
      We had a gas station out
      on the Mojave
      Weeks often passed without a car.
      I was his grease monkey
      I was not very smart
      He could do anything he wanted and I didn't care.
      Days of dust and piss
      Years passed behind the screendoor waiting
      Eternal daydream
      things we never knew time without end
    - Rainbow Brain, undated; 256772 (Box 16)
      The poem, titled "Rainbow Brain," reads:
      A true story
      Once upon a time
      there was this woman named Kacey
      Who lived in a trailor
      Across from the Shop-rite
      who used to dye the hair of all the
      Department-store beauty-queens
      who used to ride on the floats in the Orange bowl parades
      she used to dye them orange and purple and green and glitter
      that but orange bowl was only once a year
      so the rest of the time she would color her own her own hair
      all kinds of colors
      first she would dye it purple
      then she'd strip it and dye it green
      and then strip it and then do a whole
      Rainbow
      Trip on it.
      This went on
      day in and day out
      year after year
      till finally one day she just died
      At the autopsy the corner
      discovered that the dye
      had seeped down through her scalp
      and dyed her brain
      Every imaginable
      color
    - Peach Fuzz, undated (Box 16)
      The poem, titled "Peach Fuzz," reads:
      Martin Wong 141 Ridge St., #9, NY 10002598–9883
      Peach fuzz
      A true story by Martin Wong
      I think it was either Michigan Boulevard in Wisconsin or maybe
      it was Wisconsin Boulevard in Michigan
      anyway it was
      America
      Somewhere
      Brian and Jabbo were driving around
      nowhere to go
      so Jabbo he pulled down his pants
      stuck a cigarette in his big hairy butt
      and put a hat on it so it looked like a gross
      Little man with a incredibly ugly face
      and no eyes then
      they drove up to the guy on the corner
      and he says "hey man you know the way to Lakeside Drive? "
      And when the guy
      he turned around
      he was so shocked
      he puked on the spot!
    - Sign Language Art, undated; 256773 (Box 17)
      These peices show drawings of hands making American Sign Language signs for letters of the alphabet.
  - Subseries B: Art by Others, 128375
    - Kostabi mini-figures (copy), undated; 128384 (Box 3a., Folder 130)
    - Drawing: "Trent & Revonda," by John Ahearn, undated; 128383 (Box 3a., Folder 131)
    - Drawing: portrait of a man (artist unknown), undated; 128382 (Box 3a., Folder 132)
    - Copy of John Ahearn's sketchbook, undated; 128381 (Box 3a., Folder 133)
    - Painting: abstract, signed by R. Liderman, undated; 128380 (Box 3a., Folder 134)
    - Drawing: Bellevue Hospital, by Sam, Feb 2 1986, 128379 (Box 3a., Folder 135)
    - Drawing: Martin Wong, by R. Bokov, 1986, 128378 (Box 3a., Folder 136)
    - Drawing: Martin Wong, by Lee, undated; 128377 (Box 3a., Folder 137)
    - Children's artwork (?), undated; 128376 (Box 3a., Folder 138)
    - Cartoon, by S. Hernandez, 8/2/89, 1989; 256625 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Series III [A]: Catalogs, Graffiti, Invites, Posters, Source Material, etc., 128225
  Scope and Contents note
  Subject: Catalogs, Graffiti, Invites, Posters, Source Material & Source Magazines
  - Catalog: "An All-Star Salute to Chinese American Cultural Pioneers," 1993 (Wong, p.12), 128373 (Box 3a., Folder 1)
  - Catalog: "Art for Learning," 1994 (Wong, p.38), 128372 (Box 3a., Folder 2)
  - Catalog: "Daze," artwork & biography, 1986, 128371 (Box 3a., Folder 3)
  - Catalog: "Longwood Arts Journal, 1992-1993, Bronx Council on the Arts" (Wong, p.50), 128370 (Box 3a., Folder 4)
  - Catalog: "In the Looking Glass: Contemporary Narrative Painting," 1991 (c1992) (Wong, p.30-1), 1991, 1992; 128369 (Box 3a., Folder 5)
  - Catalog: Museum of the City of New York, Fall 1996 (incl. Graffiti Symposium), 128368 (Box 3a., Folder 6)
  - Catalog: New Museum of Contemporary Art, 1998 (Wong, p.2), 128367 (Box 3a., Folder 7)
  - Catalog: "In the Ring," 1993 (Wong, p.28-9), 128366 (Box 3a., Folder 8)
  - Catalog: "Simon Says," Summer 1998 (incl. Wong entry), 128365 (Box 3a., Folder 9)
  - Catalog: "The Curio Shop"/The Asian American Arts Network, 1993 (Wong, p.17), 128364 (Box 3a., Folder 10)
  - Catalog: "Martin Wong," Exit Art Show, Nov-Dec 1988, 128363 (Box 3a., Folder 11)
  - Catalog: "Contemporary Art Auction to Benefit El Bohio," Sept 1985 (incl. Wong entry), 128362 (Box 3a., Folder 12)
  - Catalog: Jane Dickson, "Paradise Alley," 1996, 128361 (Box 3a., Folder 13)
  - Catalog: Steven R. Miller (portfolio), undated; 128360 (Box 3a., Folder 14)
  - Graffiti: tag sketches, undated; 128359 (Box 3a., Folder 15)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128358 (Box 3a., Folder 16)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128357 (Box 3a., Folder 17)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128356 (Box 3a., Folder 18)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128355 (Box 3a., Folder 19)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128354 (Box 3a., Folder 20)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128353 (Box 3a., Folder 21)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128352 (Box 3a., Folder 22)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128351 (Box 3a., Folder 22)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128350 (Box 3a., Folder 23)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128349 (Box 3a., Folder 24)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128348 (Box 3a., Folder 25)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128347 (Box 3a., Folder 26)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128346 (Box 3b., Folder 27)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128345 (Box 3b., Folder 28)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128344 (Box 3b., Folder 29)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128343 (Box 3b., Folder 30)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128342 (Box 3b., Folder 31)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128341 (Box 3b., Folder 32)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128340 (Box 3b., Folder 33)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128339 (Box 3b., Folder 34)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128338 (Box 3b., Folder 35)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128337 (Box 3b., Folder 36)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128336 (Box 3b., Folder 37)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128335 (Box 3b., Folder 38)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128334 (Box 3b., Folder 39)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128333 (Box 3b., Folder 40)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128332 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 128331 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Graffiti: tag art, undated; 128330 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Graffiti: clippings, undated; 128329 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Graffiti: "Nab 2 as Transit Writers" (newspaper item), undated; 256631 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Graffiti: assorted artwork (artists incl. Crash, Stash Two, Laroc), undated; 128328 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Graffiti: layout and labels for graffiti show, undated; 128327 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Graffiti: postcard and photo, Keith Haring w/ LA2, undated; 128326 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Graffiti: mini-notebook w/descriptions of graffiti art, undated; 128325 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Graffiti: Print magazine, "Spray-can School", undated; 128324 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Graffiti: "Art from a Spray-can" (mss. draft), undated; 128323 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Graffiti: "Bizzama" artwork, signed "AMBH", undated; 128322 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Graffiti: tag art, undated; 128321 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Graffiti: "Whose to Say?" (painting, artist Jonathon), undated; 128320 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Graffiti: hip hop figure, undated; 128319 (Box 4, Folder 53 A.)
  - Graffiti: notes and comment on graffiti art, by Martin Wong, undated; 128318 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Graffiti: photo (color copy) of unidentified graffiti artists, undated; 256632 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Graffiti: photos (of unidentified graffiti artists - ?), undated; 256633 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Graffiti: "Art Boom," 1991, no.2, 128317 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Graffiti: "Coming from the Subway," Groninger Museum, 1992-1993, 128316 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Graffiti: "The Subway Sun," ca. 1987, 128315 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Graffiti: "Post-Graffiti" catalog, Sidney Janis Gallery, 1983, 128314 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Graffiti: "Wild Style" (film) pop-out 3-D logo, undated; 128313 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Graffiti: "The Devastating Artist" (drawing), undated; 256636 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Graffiti: "Wild Style" (film) logo sketches, undated; 256635 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Graffiti: "Wild Style" (film) transcript, undated; 128312 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Graffiti: "Wild Style" (film) poster and artwork, undated; 128311 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Graffiti: "Wild Style" (film) book and audiocassette, "Hip Hop Rap Music in NYC", undated; 128310 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Graffiti: "Wild Style" (film) promo flyers in Chinese, undated; 128309 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Graffiti: Museum of American Graffiti letterhead, business card, grand opening, undated; 128308 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 256637 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 256638 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 256732 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 256733 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 256734 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 256735 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 256736 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 256737 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated; 256738 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Graffiti: "Village Voice," Dec 24-30, 1980, 256739 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Graffiti: "New York Newsday," May 3, 1989, 256740 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows (n.d.), undated; 128307 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows 1984, 128306 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows 1985, 128305 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows 1986, 128304 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows 1987, 128303 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows 1988, 128302 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows 1989, 128301 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows 1990, 128300 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows 1991, 128299 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows 1992, 128298 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows 1993, 128297 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows 1994, 128296 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows 1995, 128295 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows 1996, 128294 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Invites: gallery openings & shows 1997, 128293 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Invites: gay & lesbian events, undated; 128292 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Invites: social/cultural/parties, ca. 1988-1996, 128291 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Poster: "Virtual and Interactive Arts Symposium," Feb 1992, 128290 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Poster: "Hallowe'en @ Roxy," 1992, 128289 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Poster: "2nd Annual Open Studio Chinatown Exhibition," May 1986, 128288 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Poster: "Daze & Crash: New Works," May 1990, 128287 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Poster: "Martin Wong, Semaphore East Show," Oct-Nov 1985, 128286 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Poster: "Martin Wong, Semaphore", undated (Folder 4 Right)
  - Poster: "Martin Wong: The Chinatown Paintings," Oct-Nov 1983, 128285 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Poster: "The Saint at Large Presents Hallowe'en," 1994 (incl. image of "Big Heat," by Wong), 128284 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Poster: "The Saint this Summer," 1987, 128283 (Box 5, Folder 110a.)
  - Poster: "The Saint Opening Night," Sept 26 1987, 128282 (Box 5, Folder 110b.)
  - Poster: "Exit Art," Nov-Dec 1988, 128281 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Poster: "The White Party," Feb 14 1993, 128280 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Poster: "Signs of Life Panel Discussion," 1992, 128279 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Poster: "The Eighth Annual South Bronx Show," 1987, 128278 (Box 5, Folder 113a.)
  - Source: assorted imagery (postcards, photos, etc.), undated; 128277 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Source: "Time" photos (urban commerce series), undated; 256741 (Box 13, Folder 114a)
  - Source: "My 6 Convicts" (book, c.1951), 128276 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Source: prison (assorted clippings), undated; 128275 (Box 5, Folder 115a.)
  - Source: postcard of kissing firemen (cf. Big Heat painting), undated; 128274 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Source: African-American/black people, undated; 128273 (Box 5, Folder 116a.)
  - Source: Chinatown materials & Chinese imagery, undated; 128272 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Source: Chinese imagery, undated; 256742 (Box 13, Folder 117a)
  - Source: Shanghai Museum catalog, undated; 128271 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Source: Chinese litho cards, undated; 128270 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Source: Chinese characters (script), undated; 128269 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Source: photo of Cupcake & Paco from "Short Eyes" (play) (cf. Annunciation painting), undated; 128268 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Source: sign language/the deaf, undated; 128267 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Source: astronomy/constellations, undated; 128266 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Source: boxing, undated; 128265 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Source: cowboy/western, undated; 128264 (Box 5, Folder 124a.)
  - Source: firefighters, undated; 128263 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Source: Lower East Side/graffiti/tattoos, undated; 128262 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Source: the male nude/gay erotica, undated; 128261 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Source: men in uniform, undated; 128260 (Box 5, Folder 127a.)
  - Source: Nora Wong material, undated; 128259 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Source: California redwoods, undated; 128258 (Box 5, Folder 128a.)
  - Source: works of art, undated; 128257 (Box 5, Folder 128b.)
  - Source Magazines: art, undated; 128256 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Source Magazines: art, undated; 128255 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Source Magazine: art ("Artforum"), undated; 256743 (Box 13, Folder 130a)
  - Source Magazines: Asian arts & culture, undated; 128254 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Source Magazines: Asian arts & culture, undated; 128253 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Source Magazines: Asian arts & culture, undated; 128252 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Source Magazine: Asian arts & culture, undated; 256744 (Box 13, Folder 133a)
  - Source Magazines: "Eastern Horizon" (Asian arts & culture), undated; 128251 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Source Magazines: BMX bikes, undated; 128250 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Source Magazines: boxing, undated; 128249 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Source Magazines: boxing, undated; 128248 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Source Magazines: boxing, undated; 128247 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Source Magazines: comic books, undated; 128246 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Source Magazine: comic books - "Superman vs. Muhammed Ali", undated; 256747 (Box 13, Folder 139a)
  - Source Magazines: constellations/astronomy, undated; 128245 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Source Magazines: cops, undated; 128244 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Source Magazines: erotica - firefighters, wrestling, Latin, undated; 128243 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Source Magazines: erotica - women, undated; 128242 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Source Magazines: firefighters, undated; 128241 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Source Magazines: "High Times", undated; 128240 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Source Magazines: hip hop, undated; 128239 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Source Magazines: "Int'l UFO Library Magazine", undated; 128238 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Source Magazines: "Model Railroader", undated; 128237 (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - Source Magazines: spiritual/mystical, undated; 128236 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Source Magazine: mystical/spiritual (Life: "Visions of Life after Death"), undated; 256746 (Box 13, Folder 149a)
  - Source Magazines: "Pearl Harbor", undated; 128235 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Source Magazines: prison, undated; 128234 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Source Magazines: skateboarding, undated; 128233 (Box 6, Folder 152)
  - Source Magazines: skateboarding, undated; 128232 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Source Magazines: "Thrasher" (skateboarding), undated; 128231 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Source Magazines: spanish-language, undated; 128230 (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Source Magazine: "El Vocero de Puerto Rico," Feb 2, 1991; Mar 21, 1992, undated; 256748 (Box 13, Folder 155a)
  - Source Magazines: statue of liberty, undated; 128229 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Source Magazines: tattoos, undated; 128228 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Source Magazines: "Vibe;" "Rolling Stone", undated; 128227 (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - Source Magazines: wrestling, undated; 128226 (Box 6, Folder 159)
- Series III [B]: Asian-Language Source Material, 128216
  - Chinese-language source material, undated; 128224 (Box 6A, Folder 160)
  - Chinese-language source material, undated; 128223 (Box 6A, Folder 161)
  - Chinese-language source material, undated; 128222 (Box 6A, Folder 162)
  - Chinese-language source material, undated; 128221 (Box 6A, Folder 163)
  - Chinese-language source material, undated; 128220 (Box 6A, Folder 164)
  - Chinese-language source material, undated; 128219 (Box 6A, Folder 165)
  - Japanese-language source material, undated; 128218 (Box 6A, Folder 166)
  - Chinese-language source material, undated; 128217 (Box 6A, Folder 167)
- Series IV: Biographical, 128131
  NOTE: Box 7A is labeled "Special Projects"
  - Curriculum Vitae, undated; 128215 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Birth certificate, health insurance card, Smithsonian membership, undated; 128214 (Box 6, Folder 1a.)
  - High school reunion (Class of '64), undated; 128213 (Box 6, Folder 1b.)
  - Martin Wong shows: invites & P.R. material, undated; 128212 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Artist File: compiled by Mrs. Wong Fie (mother) (ca. 1984-1991), 128211 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Artist File: compiled by Mrs. Wong Fie (mother) (ca. 1989-1993), 128210 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Artist File: Semaphore Gallery, undated; 128209 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Clippings about Wong, ca. 1984-1999, 128208 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Martin Wong scrapbook, undated; 128207 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Martin Wong scrapbook, undated; 128206 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Martin Wong publicity photo, undated; 128205 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Price lists: Semaphore Gallery (ca. 1985), 128204 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Loan agreements for art, undated; 128203 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Receipts: for sale/purchase of art, undated; 128202 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Floor plan: Wong's apartment, undated; 128201 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Leasing & apartment rental, undated; 128200 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Apartment purchase: "The Police Building", undated; 128199 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Employment: Metropolitan Museum of Art bookshop, 1986, 128198 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Worker's compensation policy, undated; 128197 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Tax documents (1981), 128196 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Medical & health-related, undated; 128195 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Sentencing agreement: NYC Parks & Recreation, July 1991, 128194 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Draft of Martin Wong catalog, works 1982-1993, 128193 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Guestbook (copy): Exit Art Gallery, show "The Social Club," Feb 1988, 128192 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Guestbook (copy): "Martin Wong, the Chinatown Paintings," Oct-Nov 1993, 128191 (Box 7, Folder 22a.)
  - 1993 mini-appointment book, 128190 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Gay & lesbian/AIDS-related, undated; 128189 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - "The Village Voice," Jun 27, 1989: "Gay Life 1989", 256759 (Box 14, Folder 24a)
  - Personal effects & mementos, undated; 128188 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Beatles scrapbook, undated; 256762 (Box 14, Folder 25a)
  - Portrait of unidentified boy, undated; 128187 (Box 7, Folder 25b.)
  - Beverly Hillbillies lunchbox, undated; 256765 (Box 7c, Folder 25c)
  - Paint palette, undated; 128186 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - San Francisco Chinese New Year parade, 1991, 128185 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Chinatown History Museum bulletins, undated; 128184 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Scholastic News bulletins, undated; 128183 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Arts journalism: by Theresa Herron, undated; 128182 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Notebook journal (in Latvian - author V. Kuypris?), undated; 128181 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Notes on "Visual Ideas", undated; 128180 (Box 7, Folder 31a.)
  - Assorted business cards, undated; 128179 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Addresses & phone numbers, undated; 128178 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Contents of Wong's wallet, ca. 1992, 128177 (Box 7, Folder 33a.)
  - Writing: "Anti-Gravity for Beginners", undated; 128176 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Writing: "The Darkness" (orig.), undated; 128175 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Writing: "The Darkness" (copy), undated; 128174 (Box 7, Folder 35a.)
  - Writing: "Das Puke Book," 1977, 128173 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Writing: "Find Me the Right Point" (orig.), undated; 128172 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Writing: "Find Me the Right Point" (copy), undated; 128171 (Box 7, Folder 37a.)
  - Writing: "Firefly Evening," 1968, 128170 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Writing: "Footprints, Poems, + Leaves" (n.d.), undated; 128169 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Writing: "Her Lips" (orig.), undated; 128168 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Writing: "Her Lips" (copy), undated; 128167 (Box 7, Folder 40a.)
  - Writing: "In Search of Holguin", undated; 128166 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Writing: "In the Ring", undated; 128165 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Writing: "The Language of the Fan" (orig.), undated; 128164 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Writing: "The Language of the Fan" (copy), undated; 128163 (Box 7, Folder 43a.)
  - Writing: "Mojave", undated; 128162 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Writing: "My Story, by Martin Wong" (mini-book), undated; 128161 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Writing: "One Night When" (orig.), undated; 128160 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Writing: "One Night When" (copy), undated; 128159 (Box 7, Folder 46a.)
  - Writing: "Sister Ed", undated; 128158 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Writing: "Skilling" (orig.), undated; 128157 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Writing: "Skilling" (copy), undated; 128156 (Box 7, Folder 48a.)
  - Writing: "The Tocci Brothers' Daring Escape" (copy), undated; 128155 (Box 7, Folder 49)